[English subtitles are available]
[الترجمة الإنجليزية متوفرة]
[See You Again]
[نراكم مرة أخرى]
[Episode 16]
[الحلقة 16]
The lion in the painting and the fish in water
الأسد في الرسم والسمكة في الماء
live in the forest
العيش في الغابة
and in the sea respectively.
وفي البحر على التوالي.
But they met in the city like this.
لكنهم التقوا في المدينة مثل هذا.
Little Turtle?
السلحفاة الصغيرة؟
You got the wrong person.
لقد حصلت على الشخص الخطأ.
♫When you first told me your name♫
♫ عندما أخبرتني باسمك لأول مرة ♫
♫I didn't hear a word you said♫
♫ لم أسمع كلمة قلتها ♫
♫Bet it was written on my face♫
♫ أراهن أنه كتب على وجهي
♫Shoulda known it was you I would love until the end♫
♫ كان يجب أن أعلم أنك كنت سأحب حتى النهاية
♫I don't know where this road leads♫
♫ لا أعرف إلى أين يقود هذا الطريق
♫All I know is I wanna go with you♫
♫ كل ما أعرفه هو أنني أريد الذهاب معك
♫In a life where there's no sure things♫
♫ في حياة لا توجد فيها أشياء مؤكدة ♫
Run. The vase here is expensive.
يجري.  المزهرية هنا باهظة الثمن.
♫I am sure I wanna live it with you♫
♫ أنا متأكد من أنني أريد أن أعيشها معك
This time,
هذا الوقت،
running is useless.
الجري لا طائل منه.
Are you okay?
هل انت بخير؟
Are you hurt?
هل تأذيت؟
♫If you look into my eyes♫
♫ إذا ​​نظرت في عيني ♫
I'm fine.
أنا بخير.
But I'm really sorry.
لكنني حقا آسف.
I accidentally
قمت بالخطأ
broke the vase here.
كسر الزهرية هنا.
♫When our time down here is spent♫
♫ عندما يقضي وقتنا هنا
May I ask who's in charge here?
هل لي أن أسأل من المسؤول هنا؟
I can compensate you.
يمكنني تعويضك.
He is
هو
the person in charge.
الشخص المسؤول.
♫It's in every single line♫
♫ يوجد في كل سطر ♫
♫I hope you know it was you that I loved until the end♫
♫ أتمنى أن تعرف أنك كنت أحببت حتى النهاية
Ayin, have some water.
عين ، بعض الماء.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
I'm not thirsty.
انا لست عطشان.
Of course you are not.
بالطبع أنت لست كذلك.
Ayin,
عين ،
your brother
أخوك
has artistic talent.
موهبة فنية.
Very gifted.
موهوب جدا.
It's just two sheep, right?
إنها شاتان فقط ، صحيح؟
Yes.
نعم.
It's just two sheep.
إنه شاتان فقط.
Do you understand art?
هل تفهم الفن
Let's look at this painting.
دعونا نلقي نظرة على هذه اللوحة.
In this painting,
في هذه اللوحة ،
he didn't use exaggerated things
لم يستخدم الأشياء المبالغ فيها
to draw attention.
لكي يلفت الانظار.
Instead, he blurred the reflection in the water.
بدلاً من ذلك ، قام بتعتيم الانعكاس في الماء.
This simple composition
هذا التكوين البسيط
shows purity.
يظهر النقاء.
It seems that he led us
يبدو أنه قادنا
into the spiritual world of the two sheep.
في العالم الروحي للخروفين.
I'll buy this painting.
سأشتري هذه اللوحة.
Into the spiritual world of the sheep?
في العالم الروحي للخراف؟
So what?
وماذا في ذلك؟
It doesn't matter what the sheep think.
لا يهم ما تعتقده الخراف.
As long as you know what Li Longda is thinking.
طالما أنك تعرف ما يفكر فيه Li Longda.
Just think of it as
فقط فكر في الأمر على أنه
his support for your brother's career.
دعمه لمهنة أخيك.
You're fooling Longda again.
أنت تخدع لونجدا مرة أخرى.
Longda.
لونجدا.
I want one too.
أريد واحد أيضا.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
Buy another one.
شراء واحدة أخرى.
Let me introduce.
دعني أقدم.
[Jin Chuan Free Photographer]
[جين تشوان المصور الحر]
My name is Jin Chuan.
اسمي جين تشوان.
I can compensate you for the vase now.
يمكنني أن أعوضك عن المزهرية الآن.
You're already talking about money.
أنت تتحدث بالفعل عن المال.
It seems that we are more than this.
يبدو أننا أكثر من هذا.
What else?
ماذا بعد؟
Although we ran away last time,
على الرغم من أننا هربنا في المرة الماضية ،
my best friend
أفضل صديق لي
helped clean up the mess.
ساعد في تنظيف الفوضى.
They were prisoned and offered compensation.
تم سجنهم وعرض عليهم التعويض.
There was a hole on that fatty's head
كان هناك ثقب في رأس ذلك الدهني
because you hit him your heel.
لأنك ضربته على كعبك.
They saw the doctor sew thirty stitches on his head
رأوا الطبيب يخيط ثلاثين غرزة على رأسه
to fix it.
لإصلاحها.
Impossible.
غير ممكن.
I remember I was using
أتذكر أنني كنت أستخدم
the tip of my shoe, not the heel.
طرف حذائي وليس الكعب.
You drank so much that day.
شربت كثيرا في ذلك اليوم.
Are you sure it's the tip of your shoe?
هل أنت متأكد من أنه طرف حذائك؟
Do the math.
احسب.
How much is it in total?
كم هو في المجموع؟
I'll pay you double.
سأدفع لك ضعف.
Okay.
تمام.
Let's friend each other on WeChat.
لنبدأ صداقات مع بعضنا البعض على WeChat.
I have no money in WeChat.
ليس لدي نقود في WeChat.
I can only use cash
يمكنني فقط استخدام النقود
or credit cards.
أو بطاقات الائتمان.
Okay.
تمام.
It's
إنه
RMB 860,000 in total.
إجمالي 860،000 يوان.
How dare you accept it?
كيف تجرؤ على قبوله؟
Don't think that we...
لا تعتقد أننا ...
We what?
نحن ماذا؟
Show me the receipts of medical fees and the vase.
أرني إيصالات الرسوم الطبية والمزهرية.
That's why we need to friend each other on WeChat.
لهذا السبب نحتاج إلى صداقة بعضنا البعض على WeChat.
I'll send you the photos once I get back.
سأرسل لك الصور حالما أعود.
I'll get you a new pair of shoes.
سأحضر لك زوجًا جديدًا من الأحذية.
Otherwise, you'll sprain your ankle.
وإلا ستلتوي كاحلك.
No need.
لا حاجة.
This will do it.
هذا سيفعل ذلك.
Now that you're here,
الآن بعد أن أصبحت هنا ،
let me show you around.
اسمحوا لي أن تظهر لك حول.
These photos were taken
تم التقاط هذه الصور
by me in recent years.
بواسطتي في السنوات الأخيرة.
No need. I have things to do.
لا حاجة.  لدي أشياء للقيام بها.
The proceeds of these photos
عائدات هذه الصور
will be donated to rescue wild animals.
سيتم التبرع بها لإنقاذ الحيوانات البرية.
Do you like elephants?
هل تحب الفيلة؟
I said no.
قلت لا.
What about monkeys?
ماذا عن القرود؟
You like little turtles.
تحب السلاحف الصغيرة.
How old are you?
كم عمرك؟
23.
23.
I'll be 24 in a few months.
سأكون 24 في غضون بضعة أشهر.
Are you still celebrating your birthday?
هل مازلت تحتفل بعيد ميلادك؟
I don't even remember
لا أتذكر حتى
the last time when I celebrated my birthday.
آخر مرة احتفلت فيها بعيد ميلادي.
I'll accompany you
سأرافقك
to celebrate your next birthday.
للاحتفال بعيد ميلادك القادم.
Little boy,
ولد صغير
no matter what you want to do,
بغض النظر عما تريد القيام به ،
you've got the wrong person.
لقد حصلت على الشخص الخطأ.
Just wait for me outside.
فقط انتظرني في الخارج.
My brother drew it.
رسمها أخي.
How is it?
كيف هذا؟
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
-He's awesome, right? -They won't recognize me.
إنه رائع ، أليس كذلك؟  -لا يتعرفون علي.
Isn't it good?
أليس هذا جيد؟
Teng Xi.
تنغ شي.
Shush.
اسكت.
Sister,
أخت،
have you seen Jin Chuan?
هل رأيت جين تشوان؟
Jin Chuan?
جين تشوان؟
He was here just now.
لقد كان هنا للتو.
Right, where is he?
صحيح أين هو؟
Is he hooking up with some girl?
هل يربط مع فتاة؟
Jin Chuan.
جين تشوان.
Miss Mumu.
ملكة جمال ريد.
Coming.
آت.
My little brother,
أخي الصغير،
I took the risk of emptying my wallet
لقد جازفت بإفراغ محفظتي
to support you.
لدعمكم.
Right, sister.
حق اختي.
Today, the two men around you
اليوم ، الرجلان من حولك
also spent a lot of money.
كما أنفق الكثير من المال.
We're afraid that no one wants to buy your paintings.
نخشى ألا يرغب أحد في شراء لوحاتك.
Really?
هل حقا؟
You're so nice to me.
أنت لطيف معي.
Mr. Li Longda bought five paintings.
اشترى السيد لي لونجدا خمس لوحات.
Chi Yu
تشي يو
bought two.
اشترى اثنين.
Miss Jin,
آنسة جين ،
are you sure they did that for me?
هل أنت متأكد من أنهم فعلوا ذلك من أجلي؟
Brother-in-law,
شقيق الزوج،
this has nothing to do with your sister.
هذا لا علاقة له بأختك.
I sincerely support your career.
أنا بصدق أؤيد حياتك المهنية.
We can go out together
يمكننا الخروج معا
when I don't have work.
عندما لا يكون لدي عمل.
I'll go there first.
سأذهب هناك أولاً.
Where did you get the money?
من أين لك المال؟
It's none of your business.
هذا ليس من شأنك.
Did you receive the money that Chi Yu's dad gave you
هل تلقيت المال الذي أعطاك إياه والد تشي يو
at the hospital that day?
في المستشفى ذلك اليوم؟
Give me the money you owe me.
أعطني المال الذي تدين لي به.
I have no money left.
ليس لدي أي نقود متبقية.
Which paintings did you buy?
ما هي اللوحات التي اشتريتها؟
That one.
هذا.
That one is pretty.
هذا جميل.
And this.
وهذا.
Walking.
المشي.
It's meaningful.
إنه ذو مغزى.
I like this too.
أنا أحب هذا أيضا.
Haoran.
حوران.
Here.
هنا.
Today,
اليوم،
to thank
أن أشكر
my brothers-in-law,
إخواني في القانون ،
let's have a celebration party tonight.
دعونا نقيم حفلة احتفال الليلة.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
You can
تستطيع
only have one brother-in-law.
ليس لديك سوى صهر واحد.
A celebration party?
حفلة احتفالية؟
Let's go.
لنذهب.
Put it here.
ضعه هنا.
This celebration party is in the wilderness.
حفلة الاحتفال هذه في البرية.
Did you lose a lot of money?
هل خسرت الكثير من المال؟
What tasty food can there be?
ما هو الطعام اللذيذ الذي يمكن أن يكون؟
I've prepared so much food.
لقد أعددت الكثير من الطعام.
We can cook on our own.
يمكننا الطبخ بمفردنا.
Stingy.
بخيل.
This is embarrassing.
هذا محرج.
I think it's quiet here.
أعتقد أن الجو هادئ هنا.
Only you
أنت فقط
can find such a good place.
يمكن أن تجد مثل هذا المكان الجيد.
Everyone is here. Come here.
الكل هنا.  تعال الى هنا.
Come here.
تعال الى هنا.
Come on.
هيا.
As usual,
كل عادة،
each of us draws a card.
كل واحد منا يرسم بطاقة.
Come on.
هيا.
Everyone draws a card.
الجميع يرسم بطاقة.
What?
ماذا؟
Draw one.
ارسم واحدة.
Let me see what card I'll draw and who will be my teammate.
اسمحوا لي أن أرى البطاقة التي سأرسمها ومن سيكون زميلي في الفريق.
Let's show our cards.
دعونا نظهر بطاقاتنا.
I got the Queen too.
حصلت على الملكة أيضا.
All right, let's assign the tasks.
حسنًا ، دعنا نسند المهام.
We
نحن
move the things in the car first.
حرك الأشياء في السيارة أولاً.
Jin Ayin and Longda,
جين عين ولونغدا ،
you clean up the place where we eat first.
تقوم بتنظيف المكان الذي نأكل فيه أولاً.
Okay.
تمام.
As for our lucky guy,
أما بالنسبة للرجل المحظوظ لدينا ،
you pitch the tent
نصب الخيمة
on your own.
لوحدك.
No.
رقم.
My leg hasn't recovered yet.
لم أتعافى من رجلي بعد.
I want to go with them.
اريد الذهاب معهم
If someone insists that his leg hurts
إذا أصر أحد على أن ساقه تؤلمه
and he can't do anything,
ولا يمكنه فعل أي شيء ،
he can just sit here
يمكنه فقط الجلوس هنا
and enjoy it.
و استمتع بها.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
Take care.
يعتني.
Hope we can have dinner as early as possible.
نأمل أن نتناول العشاء في أقرب وقت ممكن.
Let's go.
لنذهب.
Your brother is just like you.
أخوك مثلك تمامًا.
He's reasonable and adorable.
إنه معقول ورائع.
As long as people are poor,
طالما الناس فقراء ،
they can think of multiple ways.
يمكنهم التفكير بطرق متعددة.
Ayin,
عين ،
can I
هل استطيع
ask you something?
أسألك عن شىء ما؟
Go ahead.
إنطلق.
You and Chi Yu...
أنت و تشي يو ...
Are you...
أنت...
Longda.
لونجدا.
Unfold this chair.
افتح هذا الكرسي.
Otherwise, they won't have a place to sit down.
خلاف ذلك ، لن يكون لديهم مكان للجلوس.
Okay.
تمام.
So much delicious food.
الكثير من الطعام اللذيذ.
Jin Chuan,
جين تشوان
why are you just standing here?
لماذا انت واقف هنا؟
Let me help you.
دعني اساعدك.
It's okay. Let me do it.
حسنا.  دعني افعلها.
Xi,
شي ،
you helped me a lot this time.
لقد ساعدتني كثيرا هذه المرة.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Why are you being so distant?
لماذا أنت بعيد جدا؟
If it weren't for you,
إذا لم تكن لك ،
our small exhibition wouldn't have
معرضنا الصغير لن يكون
attracted so many people.
جذبت الكثير من الناس.
Back in the exhibition hall,
مرة أخرى في قاعة المعرض ،
I saw that...
رأيت ذلك...
What?
ماذا؟
Do you have someone you like?
هل لديك شخص تحبه؟
Xi,
شي ،
I know your feelings.
انا اعرف مشاعرك.
But what's between us
لكن ما بيننا
has nothing to do with anyone else.
لا علاقة له بأي شخص آخر.
It's just that a man like me
إنه مجرد رجل مثلي
is not suitable for you.
غير مناسب لك.
It doesn't matter.
لا يهم.
Because I'm suitable for you.
لأنني مناسب لك.
Xi.
شي.
I don't want to hear it.
لا اريد ان اسمعها.
Xi, don't.
شي ، لا تفعل.
I can't hear you.
لا أستطيع أن أسمعك.
Li Longda,
لي لونجدا ،
I have some drinks in my car.
لدي بعض المشروبات في سيارتي.
Go get them with me.
اذهب واحضرهم معي.
I...
أنا...
I'm not done yet.
لم انته بعد.
Come with me now.
تعال معي الان.
Why me?
لماذا أنا؟
What you need to do now is
ما عليك القيام به الآن هو
to come with me.
لتأتي معي.
Come one.
تعال واحد.
Well...
نحن سوف...
I...
أنا...
Why are you standing there and looking at me?
لماذا تقف هناك وتنظر إلي؟
Are you done?
هل انتهيت؟
What a fool.
يا له من أحمق.
You haven't finished your work yet.
لم تنته من عملك بعد.
You can ask if you don't know.
يمكنك أن تسأل إذا كنت لا تعرف.
Don't pretend that you know.
لا تتظاهر بأنك تعلم.
Why are you here?
لماذا أنت هنا؟
I'm afraid I have nowhere to sleep at night.
أخشى أنه ليس لدي مكان أنام فيه بالليل.
I'm here to help you.
أنا هنا لمساعدتك.
This is easy.
هذا سهل.
Look. I've already finished.
نظرة.  لقد انتهيت بالفعل.
Still pretending.
ما زلت أتظاهر.
Let me check it.
اسمح لي بالتحقق.
Can I leave now?
هل يمكنني المغادرة الآن؟
If I don't go back,
إذا لم أعود ،
I'll really become someone else's supporting role.
سأصبح حقًا الدور الداعم لشخص آخر.
We're supporting roles.
نحن ندعم الأدوار.
Coming.
آت.
Here.
هنا.
Wipe your hands.
امسح يديك.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Ma, what a savior.
أماه ، يا له من منقذ.
You and your brother are really different.
أنت وأخوك مختلفان حقًا.
You have the same family,
لديك نفس العائلة ،
and the same living environment,
ونفس البيئة المعيشية ،
but you like different lifestyles.
لكنك تحب أنماط الحياة المختلفة.
Actually,
في الحقيقة،
I don't know why either.
لا أعرف لماذا أيضًا.
We were both raised by grandma.
كلانا ربانا من قبل الجدة.
How come he is a tall and handsome
كيف هو طويل ووسيم
cool guy,
شاب رائع،
but I'm
لكن أنا
short
قصيرة
and poor?
والفقراء؟
Actually,
في الحقيقة،
after our dad left,
بعد رحيل والدنا ،
Abao grew up a lot overnight.
نشأ Abao كثيرًا بين عشية وضحاها.
Although
رغم
he is careless and casual
إنه مهمل وعفوي
with his friends.
مع أصدقائه.
he
هو
helped me and supported me
ساعدني ودعمتني
a lot.
كثيراً.
Jin Ayin,
جين عين ،
I like
انا يعجبني
the perseverance
المثابرة
you and your brother have.
أنت وأخوك لديكم.
Abao and I
أنا وأباو
both want to pick up grandma from the hometwon
كلاهما يريد أن يلتقط الجدة من مسقط رأسه
to let her live in a building with elevators.
للسماح لها بالعيش في مبنى به مصاعد.
So
لذا
he would secretly transfer money to me
كان يقوم بتحويل الأموال إلي سرا
and let me save it as the money to buy a house.
واسمحوا لي أن أدخرها كمال لشراء منزل.
Maybe our dream is far away,
ربما حلمنا بعيد
but
لكن
I am now
انا الان
a contract screenwriter of Jianghe Studios.
كاتب سيناريو عقد من استوديوهات Jianghe.
After I finish this script
بعد أن أنهي هذا السيناريو
and get the payment,
والحصول على الدفع ،
I'll start another project.
سأبدأ مشروعًا آخر.
Plus the money I saved...
بالإضافة إلى المال الذي وفرته ...
I'll pay back the money soon.
سأعيد المال قريبا.
Because of you,
بسببك،
I lost the money for the toilet in my elevator house.
لقد خسرت نقود المرحاض في منزلي المصعد.
I really didn't know back then.
لم أكن أعرف حقًا في ذلك الوقت.
How about this?
وماذا عن هذا؟
You can pay back the money
يمكنك تسديد المال
with interests.
مع المصالح.
Give me
أعطني
RMB 188,888.
188888 يوان صيني.
Are you blackmailing me?
هل تبتزني؟
Well,
نحن سوف،
how about...
ماذا عن...
What?
ماذا؟
Actually,
في الحقيقة،
I know
أنا أعرف
You used my card
لقد استخدمت بطاقتي
and my money
وأموالي
to keep me away from you.
ليبعدني عنك.
But what I want to say is
لكن ما أريد أن أقوله هو
no matter what we encounter,
بغض النظر عما نواجهه ،
we can face it together.
يمكننا مواجهتها معًا.
Two
اثنين
is better than one, right?
افضل من واحد صحيح؟
Jin Ayin,
جين عين ،
are you really
هل أنت حقا
in love with me?
مغرم بي؟
♫On that day♫
في ذلك اليوم ♫
♫The wind gently crosses your face♫
الرياح تعبر وجهك برفق
Shameless.
وقح.
I just want to keep an eye on you
أنا فقط أريد أن أراقبك
♫I secretly wrote it down♫
♫ كتبت ذلك سرا ♫
to make you pay back the money as soon as possible.
لحثك على سداد الأموال في أسرع وقت ممكن.
♫The first chapter of my unlikely encounter with you♫
♫ الفصل الأول من لقائي غير المحتمل معك
♫If one day♫
♫ إذا ​​ذات يوم ♫
This is for you.
هذا لك.
♫You'll wonder about me too♫
♫ سوف تتساءل عني أيضًا ♫
Don't be surprised.
لا تتفاجأ.
I'm full of skills.
أنا مليء بالمهارات.
♫That's the sound of a heartbeat♫
♫ هذا صوت دقات القلب ♫
♫A foretaste of what's to come♫
لمحة لما سيأتي
♫Maybe one day we'll meet♫
♫ ربما في يوم من الأيام سنلتقي ♫
What's this?
ما هذا؟
It's a...
انه...
♫I'm ready♫
♫ أنا جاهز ♫
A bracelet.
سوار.
♫To take you to the future♫
ليأخذك إلى المستقبل ♫
But
ولكن
my arm isn't this big.
ذراعي ليست بهذا الحجم.
♫To welcome this love♫
ليرحب بهذا الحب ♫
Give it back if you don't like it.
أعدها إذا لم تعجبك.
♫When we meet again♫
عندما نلتقي مرة أخرى
I can take it home
يمكنني أخذها إلى المنزل
and put it on Wangcai's head.
ووضعها على رأس وانجكاي.
♫It'll be the most romantic scene♫
♫ سيكون المشهد الأكثر رومانسية
Do you like it?
هل أحببت ذلك؟
♫At that moment♫
♫ في تلك اللحظة ♫
Yes.
نعم.
♫My heart is engraved with♫
قلبي محفور ♫
♫Your sweetest face♫
♫ أحلى وجه
Honey,
عسل،
look what I brought you.
انظر ماذا احضرت لك.
Honey, what's wrong?
عزيزتي ، ما الخطب؟
They seem to really like each other.
يبدو أنهم يحبون بعضهم البعض حقًا.
And I've been lying to myself.
وكنت أكذب على نفسي.
Who?
من؟
Your daughter-in-law
زوجة ابنك
and Chi Yu.
و تشي يو.
I finally have a daughter-in-law,
أخيرًا لدي زوجة ابني ،
but someone wants to take her away from me.
لكن هناك من يريد أن يأخذها مني.
Look at me.
انظر إليَّ.
Let me ask you.
دعني أسألك.
You can't live without her, right?
لا يمكنك العيش بدونها ، أليس كذلك؟
Do you really like her?
هل حقا معجب بها؟
Absolutely.
قطعاً.
Mom.
أم.
She's different from others.
إنها مختلفة عن الآخرين.
I...
أنا...
I've never seen
لم أرى أبدا
a perseverant girl like her.
فتاة مثابرة مثلها.
Sometimes people told me to
في بعض الأحيان قال لي الناس
stop being an actor
توقف عن كونك ممثلا
and to go home to do business.
والعودة إلى المنزل للقيام بأعمال تجارية.
I pretended not to care.
تظاهرت بعدم الاهتمام.
But actually,
لكن في الواقع ،
I knew I'm not confident.
كنت أعلم أنني لست واثقًا.
But Ayin is different.
لكن عين مختلفة.
She will stick with what she wants.
سوف تلتزم بما تريد.
Also,
ايضا،
she's nice to me.
إنها لطيفة معي.
Very nice.
لطيف جدًا.
Gradually,
تدريجياً،
she is not only a special person,
هي ليست مجرد شخص مميز ،
but also
ولكن أيضا
the one who makes me want to
الشخص الذي يجعلني أرغب في ذلك
become better for her.
تصبح أفضل لها.
She's the only one.
هي الوحيدة.
There was no one like her before,
لم يكن هناك أحد مثلها من قبل ،
and there will be no one like her in the future.
ولن يكون هناك أحد مثلها في المستقبل.
It looks like
يبدو
I have to use the strategy I used to conquer your father
لا بد لي من استخدام الاستراتيجية التي استخدمتها لقهر والدك
to help you.
لمساعدتك.
Remember,
تذكر،
it's too early to give up now.
من السابق لأوانه الاستسلام الآن.
Playing cat and mouse will be in vain.
لعب القط والفأر سيكون عبثا.
Pestering her will lead you to success.
مضايقتها ستقودك إلى النجاح.
Yeah!
نعم!
Help!
مساعدة!
Ayin!
الحدث!
Ayin, what's wrong?
عين ، ما الخطب؟
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Longda, why are you here?
لونجدا ، لماذا أنت هنا؟
You're so nice.
أنت لطيف جدا.
I was just thinking about buying some flowers for decoration.
كنت أفكر للتو في شراء بعض الزهور للزينة.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
These flowers are...
هذه الزهور ...
I know.
أنا أعرف.
They are for me.
هم لي.
I'm here for Ayin.
أنا هنا من أجل عين.
It's not convenient for us today.
إنه ليس مناسبًا لنا اليوم.
Nothing inconvenient.
لا شيء غير مريح.
Come in.
ادخل.
Actually, today I want to ask you to...
في الواقع ، أريد اليوم أن أطلب منك ...
It's not convenient to do anything today.
ليس من الملائم أن تفعل أي شيء اليوم.
Well.
نحن سوف.
Let me in first.
اسمحوا لي أولا.
Li Longda.
لي لونجدا.
I kindly offer you a piece of advice.
أرجو أن أقدم لك نصيحة.
A man who keeps pestering is a rascal
الرجل الذي يضايق هو الوغد
and a nuisance.
ومصدر إزعاج.
I am a nuisance.
أنا مصدر إزعاج.
I don't want it.
لا اريدها.
No need.
لا حاجة.
I...
أنا...
It hurts.
هذا مؤلم.
Chi Yu.
تشي يو.
This isn't a fair competition.
هذه ليست منافسة عادلة.
It hurts.
هذا مؤلم.
Be gentle.
كن لطيفآ.
Why did you
لماذا فعلت
do that to Longda?
افعل ذلك في Longda؟
I just wanted to.
أردت فقط أن.
Your neck is fine.
رقبتك بخير.
You need to pay attention to your waist.
تحتاج إلى الاهتمام بخصرك.
From here,
من هنا،
Xuanshu, to Mingmen, and to Yaoyangguan.
Xuanshu ، Mingmen ، و Yaoyangguan.
If you keep sitting for a long time,
إذا واصلت الجلوس لفترة طويلة ،
no one can save you.
لا أحد يستطيع أن ينقذك.
Who is this?
من هذا؟
Have you ever thought about
هل فكرت من قبل
running a small bone setting store?
تشغيل متجر صغير لتركيب العظام؟
I'll help you
سوف اساعدك
with it.
معها.
Why isn't the watch working?
لماذا لا تعمل الساعة؟
Is it dead?
هل مات؟
Charge it for me.
اشحنها لي.
Asking me to do things for you again.
يطلب مني أن أفعل أشياء لك مرة أخرى.
Why is Li Longda still here?
لماذا لا يزال Li Longda هنا؟
I'm looking for Jin Ayin.
أنا أبحث عن جين عين.
Ze.
أنهم.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Have some water.
اشرب بعض الماء.
Don't pull a long face.
لا تسحب وجهًا طويلاً.
Ze.
أنهم.
You just came back to Shanghai?
هل عدت للتو إلى شنغهاي؟
Yes, I just arrived.
نعم ، لقد وصلت للتو.
If you
اذا أنت
hadn't transferred money to me yesterday,
لم يحول لي المال أمس ،
I would have been trapped in Beijing today.
كنت لأكون محاصرا في بكين اليوم.
It's okay.
حسنا.
If you are on a business trip alone,
إذا كنت في رحلة عمل بمفردك ،
just pay attention to your wallet
فقط انتبه إلى محفظتك
and your own safety.
وسلامتك.
Okay.
تمام.
Ze,
أنهم،
have some water.
بعض الماء.
Have some water.
اشرب بعض الماء.
Okay.
تمام.
You come with me.
تعال معي.
Help me hang my clothes.
ساعدني في تعليق ملابسي.
Let's go.
لنذهب.
Have some water.
اشرب بعض الماء.
Who is that man?
من هذا الرجل؟
He...
هو...
He's hesitant when he talked and his eyes were wandering.
كان مترددًا عندما تحدث وعيناه تجولان.
He didn't even tell me his name.
لم يخبرني حتى باسمه.
It's rude.
إنه وقح.
Keep your voice down.
حافظ على صوتك منخفضًا.
He was my childhood friend.
كان صديق طفولتي.
His name is Ma Zehao.
اسمه ما زيهاو.
He's in a special situation.
إنه في وضع خاص.
His father died in an accident when he was young.
توفي والده في حادث عندما كان صغيرا.
He was alone
كان وحيدا
and often bullied.
وغالبًا ما يتعرض للتخويف.
So he is shy with strangers
لذلك فهو خجول من الغرباء
and doesn't talk much.
ولا تتحدث كثيرا.
Don't stare at him.
لا تحدق به.
And this.
وهذا.
No more aggressive look.
لا مزيد من المظهر العدواني.
Anyway, be nice.
على أي حال ، كن لطيفا.
Jin Ayin,
جين عين ،
you've been so arrogant lately.
لقد كنت متعجرفًا جدًا مؤخرًا.
No, I'm not.
لا أنا لست كذلك.
My friend is here.
صديقي هنا.
Do me a favor.
أعمل لي معروفا.
Jin Ayin,
جين عين ،
help me check it. Everything is gone.
ساعدني في التحقق من ذلك.  كل شيء اختفى.
Did you touch it again?
هل لمسته مرة أخرى؟
I don't know why either.
لا أعرف لماذا أيضًا.
No.
رقم.
You have to help me retrieve these things.
عليك مساعدتي في استعادة هذه الأشياء.
You activated the synchronization and sharing function.
لقد قمت بتنشيط وظيفة المزامنة والمشاركة.
Stop wandering around.
توقف عن التجول.
Go down.
انزل.
Take out the trash.
تخلص من الزبالة.
I forgot to introduce myself.
لقد نسيت أن أقدم نفسي.
My name is
اسمي هو
Chi Yu.
تشي يو.
Hello.
مرحبًا.
Nice to meet you.
سعيد بلقائك.
Just call me Ze.
فقط اتصل بي زي.
Ze.
أنهم.
Chi Yu got hurt when shooting,
تأذى تشي يو عند إطلاق النار ،
so he's just living here temporarily.
لذلك فهو يعيش هنا مؤقتًا.
By the way, Ayin,
بالمناسبة ، عين ،
I want to tell you
اريد ان اخبرك
Taotao's parents are not in the hospital this week.
والدا توتاو ليسا في المستشفى هذا الأسبوع.
Really? That's great.
هل حقا؟  ذلك رائع.
Indeed,
في الواقع،
we haven't visited her for a long time.
لم نقم بزيارتها منذ فترة طويلة.
You said it was inconvenient before.
لقد قلت أنه كان غير مريح من قبل.
Taotao?
من؟
Taotao is a friend of ours.
Taotao هو صديق لنا.
Yes.
نعم.
But Taotao is sick
لكن تاوتاو مريض
and has been hospitalized.
وتم نقله إلى المستشفى.
Have we
هل لدينا
met before?
التقينا من قبل؟
Really?
هل حقا؟
Ze just came back
عاد زي للتو
from Beijing this morning.
من بكين هذا الصباح.
How did you meet him?
كيف قابلته؟
Where?
أين؟
Ridiculous.
سخيف.
I was in Beijing last month.
كنت في بكين الشهر الماضي.
I just came back to Shanghai yesterday.
لقد عدت للتو إلى شنغهاي أمس.
Ayin,
عين ،
I'll pick you up first
سأقلك أولاً
when we visit Taotao this weekend.
عندما نزور Taotao في نهاية هذا الأسبوع.
Okay.
تمام.
Well,
نحن سوف،
you two keep talking.
أنتما الاثنان تواصلان الحديث.
What have you been
ماذا كنت
busy with recently?
مشغول مؤخرا؟
Working to make money.
العمل لكسب المال.
Did you get burned?
هل أحرقت؟
Hurry. Go deal with it.
عجل.  اذهب للتعامل معها.
Hurry.
عجل.
This...
هذه...
How could this happen?
كيف يمكن حصول هذا؟
What should I do?
ماذا علي أن أفعل؟
Jin Ayin, come and help!
جين عين ، تعال وساعد!
Xiang Qinyu, did you do it on purpose?
شيانغ تشينيو ، هل فعلت ذلك عن قصد؟
I didn't mean it.
لم أقصد ذلك.
If the furniture gets damaged,
في حالة تلف الأثاث ،
the landlord will be pissed off.
سوف يكون المالك غاضبًا.
I'll go to the property management department.
سأذهب إلى قسم إدارة الممتلكات.
You hold it here.
أنت تحمله هنا.
Hurry up.
عجلوا.
Ayin, how about you use this blanket
عين ، ما رأيك في استخدام هذه البطانية
to block the crack under the door?
لمنع الكراك تحت الباب؟
Okay.
تمام.
Don't remove your hands.
لا ترفع يديك.
Ze,
أنهم،
keep an eye on it for me.
راقبها من أجلي.
Don't let the water come out.
لا تدع الماء يخرج.
I'll be right back.
سأعود حالا.
Okay.
تمام.
Chi Yu.
تشي يو.
I should go.
يجب ان اذهب.
What?
ماذا؟
You
أنت
clean up yourself first.
نظف نفسك أولا.
I'll clean up myself too.
سوف أنظف نفسي أيضًا.
Ze,
أنهم،
why did you suddenly leave?
لماذا غادرت فجأة
[Where there is light, there is shadow.]
[حيثما يوجد ضوء ، يوجد ظل.]